[Music]
so welcome guys to another vlog and this
is your host high on speed and we are
heading towards
[Music]
which i am not able to trace
so right now we
m
[Music]
yo guys
hello
[Music]
oh my god
let's go
[Music]
so
so now the thing is that
the right is going smooth
and everything is going as for planned
but uh the thing is that in the briefing
uh
we just uh briefed everyone's number but
numbers
we followed whatever you gave
foreign
[Music]
and
this is the
outside this is how it looks this is an
honesty one
and this is the uh
so let's have some good food
tables reserved
riding pieces
[Music]
our official photographer for bgk thank
you
so he has bought his
camera gear
pictures
thank you so much for your dedication
we honor your uh
and you can find good videos
[Music]
thank
foreign
[Music]
this is an nh
you are i don't know this goes
on so
actually
which is a good thing
seems
so guys uh this is don cooney
as you all know
this is where in the morning
foreign
anyways guys uh
thanks for watching this vlog
i hope to see you next time
with the same spirit
thanks for watching
this is your host hi on speeds signing
off
bye
[Music]
you